this problem
asks us to demonstrate how we would
access joe's email
and sally's phone number so we can
access the
information about joe
by simply passing in the key joe smith
and when i run this code i see the value
associated with that key
however the value associated with the
key joe smith is a hash
in this problem we only want to return
one piece of information from this hash
our hash has three key value pairs we
only want to return the email
which is the value of this first key
value pair
so we know this code on line 14 returns
a hash
and to access a given value in a hash we
just need to
pass in the key so we'll again
pass in another key here on line 14
indicating that we want to access the
value associated with the key
email in this hash
and now when we run our code we see just
the email
so let's do as the problem says here
we'll access joe's email and sally's
phone number
and i'll use interpolation here
again we'll pass in the key sally
johnson
to return the hash associated with the
key
sally johnson and then we'll pass in
the key associated with her phone number
and now when we run our code we'll see
this information output nicely
you